

- kseniya7991@gmail.com
- Minsk, Belarus
- https://kseniya7991.github.io/portfolio/
- +375291715185

# Languages

#### Russian

### **English**

Pre-Intermediate Level

#### **Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS3, SCSS
- JavaScript ES6
- React.js
- BEM methodology
- Webpack, Gulp
- Node.js, Express.js
- REST API
- Mongo DB
- Figma
- Git

### Social networks

- @kseniya7991
- in kseniya
- @ksunya\_st\_

#### **Interests**

Running | Marathons, Ultramarathons

Travelling while running

### Kseniya Stoichykava

# **Junior / Trainee Fronend Developer**

#### About me

Hi, I am a junior frontend developer with 1 year training hands-on experience. I am graduated from of the Yandex.Praktikum platform. Frontend is my hobby. I have a hankering for development. Now I'm looking for my first job (trainee).

#### Education

# Marketing Manager

From September 2016 to June 2019

Belarusian State Academy of Communications Minsk

## Work experience

# Trainee Frontend Developer

From November 2020 to September Praktikum by Yandex Minsk, 2021 Remote

# **Experience:**

- coding in HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- websites and web applications development
- working with a team and code-rewievers
- enjoyment of learning

## Diploma Project - Movies

**Stack:** React.js, webpack, API, JS, express.js, MongoDB It is a portfolio project that allows you to search movies from third party API by key words, create movies, create new users on the server, register / authorize users.

### Lead Digital Marketing Manager

From April 2019 to August 2021 OMA LLC Minsk

#### **Experience:**

- writing HTML code (news pages, landings, articles), HTML emails
- preparation of technical specifications for the developer
- setting up contextual advertising (Yandex.Direct, Google Ads)
- organizing, controlling of advertising campaigns
- media planning, strategic marketing
- compilation of the semantic core

#### **Additional education**

Pre-Intermediate English, Part 1

September 2021 Puzzle English Remote

Frontend Developer

From November 2020 to September 2021

Praktikum by Yandex Remote